voiceoftv.com 2016-04-08

# Privacy Statement - Voice of TV

**1\. Introduction**  
Thank you for visiting Voice of TV’s official website. This Privacy Policy is written to better explain how we collect and use your information. This Privacy Policy is a binding contract and you must agree to it to the same extent as our Terms of Service in order to use our services.  
**  
2\. Personal Information We Collect**  
In order for you to register with us, you must, at the minimum, provide us your name, e-mail address, and date of birth. We will not disclose any information that you provide to us except in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy. 

**3\. Non-Personal Information We Collect**  
We may collect information about you that is not personal information. When you access our website, we may collect such things as your IP address, browser, operating system, referring URL, and other general information about our visitors. This information, on its own, cannot usually be used to identify you.

**4\. Use of Information**  
We may use your information:

  * To enhance or improve user experience, our website, or service.
  * To send e-mails about our site or respond to inquiries.
  * To send e-mails about VoiceofTV.com and other products, news, or updates related to VoiceofTV.com or Voice Media Company projects.

**  
5\. Login Information**  
You will be able to create a unique login using your e-mail address and password when you sign up to VoiceofTV.com. We remind you that account sharing is prohibited by our Terms of Service. If you have reason to believe that your account security has been compromised, or if you are unable to login to your account, you should use our password recovery tool to reset your login information. If you are still unable to login, or if the e-mail address associated with your VoiceofTV.com account has also been compromised, you should notify us so that we can take action to secure your account.

**6\. Cookies**  
In order to distinguish you from other users—especially other users on the same network as you—we need to use cookies to track your specific computer. These cookies are used to save your preferences, as well as to keep track of advertisements. For these reasons we require that you keep cookies enabled when using our website.

**7\. Third Party Websites**  
We may link to third party websites from our own website. We have no control over, and are not responsible for, these third party websites or their use of your personal information. We recommend that you review their privacy policies and other agreements governing your use of their website.

**8\. Third Party Access to Your Information**  
We protect your information from being accessed by third parties. However, since we may employ outside maintenance personnel or use a third party to host our material, there are third party entities which may have custody or access to your information. Because of this, it is necessary that you permit us to give access to your information to third parties to the same extent that you authorize us to do so. For greater certainty, every authorization which you grant to us in this Privacy Policy, you also grant to any third party that we may hire, contract, or otherwise retain the services of for the purpose of operating, maintaining, repairing, or otherwise improving or preserving our website or its underlying files or systems. You agree not to hold us liable for the actions of any of these third parties, even if we would normally be held vicariously liable for their actions, and that you must take legal action against them directly should they commit any tort or other actionable wrong against you.

Additionally, we may store your information or share it with certain other third parties for reason that may or may not be related to maintenance, advertising, marketing, or other purposes related to our business. For example, without limiting the generality of the foregoing, we employ Google Adsense, which uses the DoubleClick cookie to better target advertisements that you may be interested in.

**9\. Law Enforcement**  
We may disclose your information to a third party where we believe, in good faith, that it is desirable to do so for the purposes of a civil action, criminal investigation, or other legal matter. In the event that we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either. Please note that our disclosure is not limited to the purposes of Dutch law, and we may, at our discretion, exercise our rights under this paragraph pursuant to any investigation or other legal matter from any jurisdiction, provided that it is in relation to the enforcement of a law which would, if enacted in the Kingdom of the Netherlands, be constitutionally valid.

**10\. Security of Information**  
We use SSL certificates to help secure our website. However, we make no representations as to the security or privacy of your information. It is in our interest to keep our website secure, but we recommend that you use anti-virus software, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security threats.

**11\. California Online Privacy Protection Act**  
Although we are not located in California, we do permit California users to access our website and we intend to comply fully with California’s privacy laws. If you have any questions about your rights under this Privacy Policy, please contact us for more information.)

**12\. Statement Regarding the European Data Protection Directive (Directive 95/46/EC)**  
In compliance with the European Data Protection Directive, we hereby notify you that your data may be stored and transferred in accordance with the terms laid out in our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy. Your agreement to the Terms of Service and Privacy Policy constitutes your consent to transfer your data to the recipients described within those documents. The controller of your data, for your information, is:

Voice Media Company (Europe)  
Cruquius 34  
3825 MH Amersfoort  
The Netherlands

You can contact us here

**13\. Use of Service by Minors**  
If you become aware of anyone who is accessing our service in violation of the applicable laws regarding minors, please notify us immediately. This means that anyone who is less than sixteen years old and is accessing our service without parental consent, or in the case of a resident of the United States, is less than thirteen years old regardless of parental consent, should be reported to us immediately.

**14\. Amendments**  
We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, and the amended version will be posted on our website in place of the old version. We will also include the date that the currently displayed Privacy Policy took effect to help you determine whether there have been any changes since you last used our website. Like our Terms of Service, you must visit this page each time you come to our website and read and agree to it if the date it was last modified is more recent than the last time you agreed to the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the new Privacy Policy, you must immediately cease using our service.

**15\. Contact**  
Any inquiries about your rights under this Privacy Policy, or any other matters regarding your privacy, contact us.
